<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="app_name">ProAuth</string>
    <string name="app_package_name">com.example.proauth</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="hello_world_main">Main ProAuth page will be directory to app management, history, etc. </string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    
    <string name="title_manage_apps">Manage Your Apps</string>
    
    
    
    <string name="dummy">UncreativeDummyString</string>
    
    <string name="title_lockscreen">Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="no_description"></string>
    <string name="app_is_locked"><b>This application is locked by ProAuth. (Default pass: 1234)</b>\n Enter your password.</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="security_settings">Security Settings</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="which_app_is_locked">to unlock it.</string>
    
    
    <string name="title_activity_conv">Convenience Activity</string>
    <string name="convenience_contents">Handy dandy place to do things.\n</string>

    
    <string name="password_screen"> Input the password</string>
    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_message">My message</string>
    <string name="service_running">The service is running</string>
    
    <string name="activity_name_pattern">Start.*cmp=([\\w\\._]*)/([\\w\\._]*)</string>
    <string name="intent_name_pattern">.*cmp=([\\w\\._]*)/([\\w\\._]*)</string>
    <string name="get_log_command">logcat ActivityManager:I *:S</string>
    <string name="clear_log_command">logcat -c</string>
    
    
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQActivity</string>
    <string name="faq_contents">Welcome to ProAuth and our FAQ and Tutorial! \n

Tutorial \n
1. Go to Manage Your Apps. The default password is "1234." \n
Here, the security levels of each of your apps are \n
listed, and you can choose what security settings you want. Putting an app at \n
security level MEDIUM, for example, lets you access that app while your phone \n
is still with you. \n
 \n
2. Go to ProAuth Settings. Here, some recommended settings are chosen for you. \n
You can change your password here, as well as enable or disable the triggers \n
that proauth uses to determine phone state. \n
Change the list of triggers until you are satisfied with how ProAuth will work, \n
and then start your service by checking "Start Monitoring Service." \n
ProAuth is now up and running! \n
 \n
FAQ \n
Q: What is ProAuth? \n
A: ProAuth is short for progressive authentication. This app lets you type in  \n
your password less often than the stock lock screens because it makes your phone \n
aware of how safe it is, as well as how dangerous your apps are. \n
For example, under the default settings, your phone will never ask you for  \n
your password if you are still holding on to it, and it will automatically  \n
lock itself again when you have left it on a table for a while. \n
 \n
Q: What do the security states mean? \n
A: The security states represent two things: \n
	1. For the full system, it represents how safe your phone feels \n
		When you log in at any lock screen, your phone state will be \n
		jumped to PRIVATE. When you leave your phone alone for a while, \n
		it will drop security levels until it hits PUBLIC. \n
	2. For each app, it represents how dangerous it is. \n
		PRIVATE apps are only available when the phone is in state \n
		PRIVATE, and on the other extreme, PUBLIC apps are always \n
		available. \n
 \n
After 30 seconds, it will lock all the apps categorized as PRIVATE, then after \n
another 30 seconds, it will also lock all the apps categorized as HIGH.  \n

        
    </string>
    
</resources>